

PROFILE STATEMENT

Mentally Strong, passionate worker specialized in GIS. Sacrificing and cooperative with strong communication skill. Bilingual in Korean and English. Certificates in GIS and Microsoft Office programs. 120+hours of volunteer service and 2 years of service in the Korean Air force. Flexible and adaptable to work in changing environment.

EDUCATION

Master of Science / Geospatial Technologies

University of Washington Tacoma, WA. Sep 2020 – Present (Anticipated Graduation: Aug 2021)

- Cumulative GPA: 4.0 / 4.0
- Upsilon Sigma Honor Society

Bachelor of Arts / Urban Studies

University of Washington Tacoma, WA. Sep 2013 – Aug 2018

- Cumulative GPA: 3.63 / 4.0
- Tau Sigma Honor Society
- Omicron Delta Kappa Honor Society

EXPERIENCE

Marketing Associate

MERGE HOLDINGS, Seoul, South Korea. / Aug 2019 - Nov 2019

- Worked as a marketing associate at MERGE HOLDINGS, mainly planned and created in-app contents to promote the app uses.
- Managed the information about the local and franchise stores that are in partnership.

Data Curation Associate

Lyft Corporation, Bellevue, WA. / Dec 2018 - May 2019

- Worked as a data curation associate at Lyft's L5 Autonomous Vehicle OSM mapping team through Ryzen Solutions.
- Used OSM and JOSM to perform highly detailed analysis, edits, and quality control to OSM data.

CONTACTS

Email:

jeminkang1991@gmail.com

Phone: 971 380 9278

Address: 3105 S 47th Street,

Tacoma, WA. 98409

PORTFOLIO

Wix

https://jkang11.wixsite.com/jeminkang

Github

https://jkang11.github.io/By-jkang11/Portfolio/

LANGUAGES

Korean: Native English: Fluent

SKILLS

ArcGIS JavaScript

QGIS CSS
OSM HTML

JOSM Python

Microsoft Office

CERTIFICATE

GIS Certificate

from University of Washington Tacoma

Microsoft Office Specialist from Microsoft Corporation

GIS Intern

Safe Street Campaign, Tacoma, WA. / Oct 2018 - Nov 2018

- Worked as a GIS intern mainly utilizing GIS software and the U.S. Census data.
- Created multiple thematic maps such as crime report maps and socio-economic status maps that helped the company's decision-making process.

Korean Class Instructor

University of Washington Tacoma, WA. / Mar 2018 – May 2018

- Taught basic Korean to average of 15 students.
- Organized and prepared materials for each class.

VOLUNTEER WORK

The Autism Korea

Seoul, South Korea. / Jun 2017 - Dec 2017

- Helped the students to understand and focus on the job training session at the Autism center.
- Spent a total of 104 hours as a volunteer.

Gonbler

Seoul, South Korea. / Jul 2017 – Sep 2017

- Volunteered as a mentor for students preparing for study abroad.
- Posted useful information related to study in the United States.

Sang-II District Children Care

Seoul, South Korea. / Jan 2015 – Mar 2015

- Taught basic English including grammar, speaking, and reading to average of 10 children.
- Spent a total of 20 hours as a volunteer.

Military Service

Republic of Korea Air Force

Seoul, South Korea. / Jun 2015 – Jun 2017

- Worked with military dog to provide safety for the President of South Korea when he/she visits the airport located in the Seong-Nam Air Force base.
- Detected explosives that can be potential threat to the President of South Korea.
- Trained military dogs for both detecting explosives and guarding the base.